At the age of becoming a mother of small children,
I myself am becoming a little girl.
And my sister started using this product again and again.
Wow!  Now sister is coming to our house for the first time with her daughter.
So I
bought this cute dress for her from the market yesterday
which also has a cute cap and purse.
But mom is saying that you forgot to bring the plate, bowl and
spoon.  So we
quickly took out the car and came first to
pick up Mota Bhai.  And as soon as he came, Maharaj ji said that it is
shining very brightly today.  What is the secret?
Hey, Raj is Raj.  My aunt's daughter is
coming to our house for the first time with her daughter.
And second, this instant glow
comes from this Dum Dog purple sunscreen.  Its purple
tint neutralizes Indian skin tone and
creates an even tone.  And with SPF 50
protection, it contains 4% new Cinnamide that will
remove blemishes and brighten skin.
Moreover, it is non-greasy and lightweight.  And
brother, I
also apply this Dum Dog 2% Kojic Acid Night Cream every night before sleeping,
which removes all the pigmentation dark spots and
repairs the skin.
Because it contains kojic acid, new cinnamides,
alpha and butene.  Now brother, do you understand
why I am telling you all this in detail
?  Because this is the gift I want
on Rakshabandhan.  If you also want Derm's Purple
Sunscreen and 2% Kojic Acid Night Cream,
I'll tag along.  Order from perp.com.
Now when I reached the market, I came to know that the
market was closed today.  So we
bought some snacks and after reaching home,
welcomed sister with cold drinks and snacks.
Also got a photo taken of the fourth generation in one frame.
Gave a gift to Babu.
Today the owner of the property and my aunt also started
taking photographs and made me the photographer,
Radhe-Radhe.